under insurance company prudential
insurance and kenya education fund the
partnership has seen 100 students
between form 1 and form 4 fully paid for
school fees and 16 000 revision books
are printed and distributed across the
nation announcing a new scholarship
program starting in may in may of this
year where we've taken a cohort of 85
students and we're going to be paying
for school fees for for ones from twos
from trees and full force why are we
doing that because we believe that the
that this country is still
encountering the impact of covet 19. a
lot of our people lost their jobs and as
a result they are not able to afford
school fees for their kids and so this
is us coming together to say we support
the community within which we work with
and that's how we demonstrate our
support
barring county has for the first time
directly exported its coffee months
after up